(Leonard:)Really?
(Sheldon:)How those nipples feeling, chief?
(Bernadette:)Penny, can we please get our drinks?
(Penny:)Yeah, hang on, just give me sec.
(Amy:)At work today, I did
an in vivo stereotaxic surgery.
(Bernadette:)Cool. At my lab, I performed
ten laser capture micro-dissections.
(Penny:)I scraped gum
off the bottom of that table.
Only because my manager
saw me put it there.
(Amy:)Oh, my gosh.
(Amy:)That's the girl
that broke Rajesh's heart.
(Bernadette:)That's Lucy?
(Penny:)I don't know why but I always
pictured her as Indian.
(Bernadette:)I think that reason's called racism.
(Penny:)I'm gonna go talk to her.
(Bernadette:)Why? What are you gonna say?
(Penny:)I'm not gonna say anything.
I just want to check her out.
(Penny:)Because she hurt my friend.
My Indian friend.
(Penny:)Who's racist now?
(Bernadette:)You because you just called him
your "Indian friend."
(Penny:)Yeah, well, you're short.